等等
Wait.
先歇一会  然后我们就快到了
Take a minute, then we're almost there.
还有三英里
About three miles out.
你开玩笑吧
You can't be serious.
达里尔刚刚才叫我们回家
Daryl just told us to go home.
我可没听到
I didn't hear that.
我觉得他暗示了
Well, I think he was being subtle.
他说他们有望风的
He said they were armed with lookouts.
达里尔知道我绝对不会回头
And Daryl knows I would never turn back.
你要怎么继续前进  玛姬
How're you gonna keep going, Maggie, huh?
带上什么军队
With what army?
拜托  小加  帮我说句话
Come on, Gabe, back me up here.
我们的人快饿死了
Our people are about to starve.
没找到粮食  我是不会回到家人身边的
I'm not going back to my family having failed.
天啊
Oh, Jesus.
至少承认你对我们的要求很过分
At least admit what you're asking of us --
为了一袋豆子逼我们去送死
walking to our deaths for what, a sack of beans?
如果你更想拯救自己
If you're more interested in saving yourself
而不是保护家里的人
than protecting the people back home,
那你可以走了
you can go.
我们不需要你
We don't need you.
我们都知道那不是真的
We both know that's not true.
好  这样吧
Alright, tell you what.
你向我保证一件事
You make me a promise --
在该死的牧师面前
in front of the goddamn preacher --
我就留下来
and I will stick around.
向你保证什么
Promise you what?
我为你做这件事
I do this for you,
那我们就扯平了  两不相欠
and we're even, we are good.
我不用一直担惊受怕
I don't have to keep looking over my shoulder.
我们永远不会扯平
We will never be even.
那你就要少一个你极度需要的士兵了
Then you are gonna be down a soldier that you desperately need.
你来决定
Your call.
你愿意接受我的保证
You'd take a promise from me?
真的吗
Really?
是啊  谁不会呢
Yeah. Who wouldn't?
我猜你是个信守承诺的女人
I'm assuming you are a woman of your word.
我一直都是个信守承诺的男人
I've always been a man of mine.
怎么了
What is it?
是他妹妹的闺蜜
It's his sister's best friend.
特蕾莎
Teresa.
她只是个孩子
She was just a kid.
我们必须杀掉他们
We have to get them.
杀光他们所有人
All of them.
你们也认识黑胡子吗
Y'all know Blackbeard, too?
等等
Wait.
还能找到更多吗
Think we can find more?
行尸走肉
第十一季  第七集
你做得挺好
You're doing great.
我做得还行  不算挺好
I'm doing okay, not great.
你自我评判时该考虑到
The timeline since this was last
战斗成为你日常生活中
an essential activity in your daily routine
必不可少的活动
and the necessity for it
已经是很久以前的事了  而且现在也没必要了
should be factors in your self-judgment.
军队会帮我们杀行尸
The military does this for us.
我已经很久没有亲自动手了
It's been so long since I've had to.
原来这并不像骑自行车
It's not like riding a bicycle, turns out.
这种事你是会忘记的
You do forget.
这是小脑在保护你
That's the good ol' cerebellum
远离不愉快的回忆
protecting you from unpleasant memories.
我记得美好的回忆
I remember the good stuff.
史蒂芬妮  我得问一句
Stephanie, I-I have to ask.
你认识霍恩斯比很久了吗
You've known Hornsby a long time?
挺久的  怎么了
Pretty long, why?
他能不能处理我们的...
Is he capable of taking care of our...
越轨行为
transgressions?
换而言之
In other words,
这些苦力活真的能让我们获得自由吗
will all this labor truly lead to our freedom?
如果他说会  那就会
If he says it will, it will.
兰斯有自己的行事方式
Lance has his own way of doing things.
但你可以信任他
But you can trust him.
你会知道的
You'll see.
-让我来接手  -我可以
- Whoa. Let me take over. - I got this.
我可以帮忙  没事的
I can help, it's fine.
-不  有事  -会没事的
- No, it's not! - It will be.
以西结
Ezekiel!
怎么了
What?
我爱你  但你得给我点空间
I love you, but you got to give me space, man.
你能拖走它们吗
Can you just clear these?
天啊
God!
我应该都杀完了
Think I got the last of them.
-你没事吧  -嗯
- You okay? - Yeah.
没事
Fine.
抱歉  我不是有意朝你发火的
Sorry, I didn't mean to snap at you.
只是里面太挤了
It's just so cramped in there.
没事
Nah, it's cool.
以西结  我能做些什么吗
Ezekiel, what can I do?
只是灰尘太大了
It's -- It's dusty.
肯定是因为这个
I'm sure that's it.
需要我们帮忙清理你们的区域吗
Y'all need help clearing your area?
史蒂芬妮  我们还得搞多久
Steph, how much longer we got to do this?
已经好几天了
It's been days.
还要几天吧  我猜
Uh, a couple more, I guess.
他撑不了几天了
He won't make it a few more days.
我没事
I'm fine.
不  你得去看医生
No, you need to see a doctor.
我是不会抛下你一个人在这里干活的
I'm not gonna leave you alone to work out here.
别犯蠢了
Don't be stupid!
没错  我说出来了
Yeah, I said it.
他们有正儿八经的医院什么的
They got real hospitals and shit here.
你能帮帮忙吗
Can you make that happen?
可以啊  我马上去找霍恩斯比先生
Uh, yeah, I'll talk to Mr. Hornsby right now.
谢谢  我们非常感激
Thank you. We are much obliged.
如果我们又要通过劳动还这个人情...
If this becomes another debt we have to work off...
我从来不怕劳动
Never been afraid of hard work.
但我不喜欢朋友因固执而死
Kinda anti friends who die from stubbornness.
默瑟  这里离脏佬工作的地方太近了
Mercer, this is way too close to where the nasties are working.
这味道简直...恶心
The smell is... revolting.
那家伙是谁
Who the hell was that?
我们的招募员对你印象深刻
Our recruiters were incredibly impressed with you.
是吗
Were they?
我还以为他们会觉得我很难搞
I-I thought maybe they found me difficult.
我们料想到了你这种背景的人会要求比较高
Well, we expect a person with your pedigree to have high standards.
在联邦里反正是这样的
We certainly do at State.
弥尔顿女士对她的哈佛校友很有好感
Well, Ms. Milton has great affection for her fellow Harvard grads.
你应该很容易就能获得一个职位
Should be no trouble finding a position for you.
我很乐意为你们工作  换取对我社区的援助
I'm happy to work to pay for the aid for my community,
但我不会在这里久留
but I'm not staying here permanently.
我只想声明一下这点
I just want to make that clear.
你见过弥尔顿女士之后  也许会重新考虑
After you meet Ms. Milton, you might reconsider.
我更想见到我的朋友们
I'd rather see my friends.
话说  有人能带我去他们工作的地方吗
Actually, can somebody take me to where they're working, please?
他们违法了
They broke the law.
霍恩斯比先生安排他们接受惩罚后
Mr. Hornsby has arranged for their release
会释放他们的
with a fine that they're repaying.
什么
What?
嗯  他们应该正在为未来的发展
Yeah, I believe they're clearing buildings
清理建筑物
for future development.
具体是在清理什么
Clearing them of what, exactly?
行尸
The dead.
好的  所以他们被派去清理行尸几天几周
Okay, so they're assigned to clear walkers for days, weeks?
或许是几个月
Months, maybe?
与此同时你们希望我提供法律服务给...
And I'm expected to provide legal services to --
弥尔顿女士和她的内阁
Ms. Milton and her cabinet.
对
Right.
那我想和她谈谈
Then I'd like to speak with her.
立刻谈  谢谢
Right away, please.
这比较困难
Well, that would be difficult.
这又是为什么
Why is that exactly?
这和霍恩斯比先生预想的时机不太一样
It's just Mr. Hornsby's expectations of the timing were a little different.
他是你的上司吗
Is he your supervisor?
不是
No.
那我希望立刻和她谈
Then I'd like to speak to her right away.
拜托了
Please.
走吧  小子
Come on, boy.
那里面需要我帮忙吗
You need any help in there?
不用
No.
抽一根吗
You want one?
好啊
Sure.
给
Here you go.
谢了
Thanks.
他们回来了
Here they come!
开门
Open up!
这就开
On it, on it!
听上去是巡逻队回来了
Sounds like patrol has come home.
-放他们进来  -嗯
- Yo, let them in. - Yep.
在主里死去的人有福了
Blessed are the dead who die in the Lord,
圣灵说  是的  他们脱离劳苦得享安息
even so saith the Spirit, for they rest from their labors.
我们说  愿主与你和你的灵同在
We say, "The Lord be with you and thy Spirit."
阿门
Amen. Amen. Amen.Amen.
如果你妹妹还活着  我们会找到她的
If your sister's out there, we'll find her.
我们还会把这些凶手一个个找出来
And every last one of these murderers.
一个不落
All of them.
但那个人  他归我
But the one -- he's mine.
到处都有侦察兵
There are scouts everywhere.
我会小心的
I'll be careful.
如果你有机会除掉他们中的一员
If you get a chance to kill one of them,
如果有人落单  而你处于上风...
if he's alone and you have the advantage...
我会动手的
I will.
准备好了吗
You ready?
我不对我认识的人动刀
I'm not cutting up anyone I know.
你得给我找四个陌生人
You're gonna have to find me four strangers.
三个就够了
Only need three.
出于实用和留念  我还留着我的面具
I kept my mask for practical and sentimental reasons.
这事不是开玩笑
This is not fun.
你这态度可不行
Well, not with that attitude.
我们速战速决吧
Let's get it over with.
我们搜了三条线
We did three different sweeps.
到处都没有踪迹  长官
No signs of tracks anywhere, sir.
湖边的建筑搜了吗
You try the buildings out by the lake?
搜了  长官
Yes, sir.
-铁路沿线呢  -搜了  长官
-Along the train tracks? -Yes, sir.
公路下的通道呢
Freeway underpasses?
-搜过了  长官  -够了
-Yes, sir. -Oh, come on!
外面可是有几十个混蛋
There are dozens of these assholes out there!
-教皇  -不
- Pope. - No!
你们的兄弟死了
Your brothers are dead!
不感到羞愧吗
Are you not ashamed?!
还是说你们觉得这是可以接受的
Or do you think this is acceptable?!
他们是在听从我的建议
They were following my recommendations.
我告诉了他们最后一队去了哪里
I told them where the last teams went.
我告诉了他们接下来去哪里
I told them where to go next.
你想吼谁的话
You want to scream at somebody,
来吼我
scream at me.
你想当圣人吗  是这样吗  肖
You trying to be noble? Is that it, Shaw?
你想让他们喜欢你吗
You trying to get them to like you?
试试让他们活着
Try keeping them alive.
冲他们吼就能实现吗
And yelling at them is gonna do that?
让自己有点用
Go be useful.
带上你的男人
Take your boy over there
去找到那群该死的敌人
and go and find my goddamn enemies!
走吧  我们有命令了
Come on. We have orders.
留下
Stay.
你没事吧
You alright?
没事
I'm fine.
你刚才帮他们说话
I'm sure the guys are grateful
那些人肯定很感激你
for what you did back there.
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
换我肯定会
I'd be.
我不知道
I don't know.
可能是做了件蠢事
It may have been stupid.
不  你们找到了一个好地方
No, you got a good place.
我相信背后的故事一定很精彩
I'm sure there's a good story that goes with it.
你和那些人相处过一段时间
Well, you spent some time with those people.
我相信他们也有自己的版本
I'm sure they have their sides.
不  完全没有
No, not at all.
我们需要一个地方
Well, we needed a place.
我们找到了一个
We found one.
剩下的你可以自己脑补
You can fill in the rest.
你对此有什么想说的吗
You got something to say about it?
没有  我只是很惊讶
No. I'm just surprised is all.
为什么惊讶
Surprised why?
你们赢了
You won.
你们有围墙  有食物
You got the walls. You got the food.
为什么还要继续猎杀
Why keep hunting?
我们得确保他们不会再回来
We have to make sure they don't come back.
好吧
Okay.
你不明白
You know, you don't understand.
你自己一个人在外面很轻松
It's easy for you out here on your own,
只要考虑自己就行了
only having to worry about yourself.
我们需要保护整个社区
We have a whole community to protect.
我们有组织架构
And we have a structure.
有领袖带我们走到这里
And a leader who got us this far.
刚才发生的事情
What happened back there --
并不是常态
that was -- that wasn't normal.
是的  我遇见过那样的人
Yeah, I met guys like that before.
教皇有问题要解决  他被激怒了
Pope's got a puzzle to solve, and he's riled up.
这些人怎么会这么难找
How can these people be so hard to find?
所以  你杀掉所有人
So, you kill everybody,
然后他变回好人吗
and then he goes back to being a good guy?
他就像是我的父亲
He's like a father to me.
没人相信我时  他相信我
He believed in me when no one else would.
他让我变得更坚强
He made me strong.
我认为你不需要任何人来让你变得坚强
I doubt you ever needed anyone to make you strong.
肩膀放低
Lower your shoulders.
手臂松弛
Arms limp.
不错  玛姬
That's good, Maggie.
绑回树上
Back to the tree.
真是垃圾
This piece of shit.
不会和你完美贴合的
It's not gonna fit you perfectly.
这是别人的脸
It was... someone else's face.
这样也许真的能行
Look, this might actually work.
我是认真的
And I mean it.
如果我能做到  你也能做到
If I can do it, you can do it.
我把这个拿回去
I'll take this back,
改成适合你的大小
work on it, fix it for you.
然后我们再试一次
Then we'll try it again.
你刚才做得很好  玛姬
You did good, Maggie.
在主里死去的人有福了
Blessed are they who die in the Lord,
圣灵说  是的
so saith the Spirit.
在主里死去的人有福了
Blessed are they who die in the Lord,
圣灵说  是的  他们脱离劳苦得享安息
so saith the Spirit, for they rest from their labors.
在主里死去的人
Blessed are they who --
告诉我  上帝
Tell me, Father.
您引领我度过最黑暗的时光
You have guided me through the darkest of times.
我珍视我们的对话和您给予我的指引
I treasure our conversation and the guidance you have given me.
有什么事情需要我知道吗
Is there anything I should know?
谢谢您  上帝
Thank you, Father.
今日就加入联邦军队
Enlist in the Commonwealth Army today.
帮助守护...
Help protect --
你休息多长时间
How long is your break?
时间不长
Not long.
只够带你看看我的宿舍  然后就回去
Just enough to show you my dorm room and then get back.
你在这里一直住宿舍吗
You've always lived in a dorm here?
是的  很不错
Yeah. It's great.
托米  抱歉
Tomi, I'm sorry.
我不懂你为什么不想要
I-I just don't understand why you wouldn't want the life
在这里当医生  过更好的生活
that comes along with being a doctor here.
我不想回到过去
I don't want to go back to before.
这又不一样
Well, it wouldn't be the same.
爸爸没在这里给你施压
Dad isn't here to put pressure on you.
不只是因为爸爸
It wasn't just Dad.
你喜欢那种生活  但我不喜欢
And you liked that type of life, but I didn't.
永不松懈  永不休息
Never turning it off, never sleeping,
一切都运转得过快
everything moving too fast.
为了工作一直忙到累死
People who burn themselves out for work
或想自杀为止吗
until they die or want to?
为社区安全尽你的一份力
Do your part to keep our community safe.
你以前很喜欢那份工作的
Hey, you used to love the job.
我还记得你以前救人后
I remember how you used to look when you saved someone,
-还有你告知病人好消息后的表情  -求你停下
- when you told somebody good news. - Please stop. Please stop.
坐下
Sit.
不能有人知道我曾是医生  懂吗
No one can know that I was a doctor, okay?
答应我
Promise me.
-这是什么意思  -相信我  好吗
- What does that mean? - Just trust me, okay?
我喜欢现在的状态
I like things the way they are.
这地方行得通
This place makes sense.
-这里有秩序  体制  -好
- There's order, a system - Okay!
好
Okay.
行吧
Fine.
今日就加入联邦军队
Enlist in the Commonwealth Army today.
帮助守护你的邻居和我们的家园
Help protect your neighbors and defend our home.
记住  我们同舟共济
Remember, we're all in this together.
我过会儿要和帕梅拉·弥尔顿见面
I have a meeting with Pamela Milton later.
我应该知道些什么吗
Anything I should know?
这真是好事
That's nice for you.
像我这样的人永远见不上弥尔顿女士
Someone like me would never meet Ms. Milton.
为什么
Why not?
你必须知道自己的位置
You have to know your place.
你
You.
你们以为我做了什么
What do you think I did?
我没做错任何事  我发誓
I did nothing wrong, I swear.
住手  我是他的律师
Stop! I'm his lawyer.
-他有权听到自己的权利  -由美子  不要
He's entitled to hear his rights. Miko, Miko, no.
-由美子  别管了  -快走
- Miko, leave it alone. - Come on. Move it.
这就是联邦之道
That's the Commonwealth way.
我说过你会学会的
I told you you'd get it right.
恭喜  不用谢
Congrats and you're welcome.
他变了吗
Has he changed?
我们不能冒险知道
We can't know that.
他有作用
He's helpful.
他会起作用
He would be,
只要对他来说还有好处
long as there's something in it for him.
那你的承诺呢
So, your promise?
我希望我能遵守
I hope I can keep it.
关注一下你想要哪个
You know, keep an eye open for which one you want,
只要我们开始补充  你就能第一个选
because as soon as we restock, you've got first dibs.
我得跟你谈谈
Hey! I need to talk to you.
-我哥在哪  -他没事
- Where the hell is my brother? - He's fine.
这不是我的问题
That wasn't my question.
你和帕梅拉约好见面
You made an appointment with Pamela,
即使是在我对你和你的朋友们说
even after I told you and your friends
我正在处理一切之后
that I was taking care of things.
你差点搞砸了一切
You almost screwed everything up.
你从街上绑走了我哥
You kidnapped my brother off the street.
有道理
Fair enough.
他今晚就会回家  我只需要这么多时间
He'll be home tonight. That's how much time I need.
要这时间干什么
For what?
好  情况是这样  很简单
Alright, it works like this. It's real simple.
你的人需要帮助  对吧
Your people need help, right?
而你想要你犯了法的朋友们获得自由
And you want your friends, who broke the law, to go free.
这些都是很难办的事
Those are big asks.
我能为你办到
I can deliver for you.
你一定能得到某些好处
There must be something in it for you.
一个位高权重的朋友
A friend in high places.
日后我可能需要帮助
Someday, I might need a favor,
而你可能会还我这个人情
and you might be favorably inclined.
你怎么说
So what do you say?
你能再等几个小时吗
Can you sit tight for a few more hours?
只有几个小时
A few hours.
太好了
Excellent.
巡逻队彻查过这里
Patrol has been all through here.
他们搜过几英里内的每栋建筑
They've checked every building for miles.
应该没人来过的
These trails should be cold.
看起来有人来过
Well, it looks like someone's been through here.
小心
Heads up.
出来  举起手
Come out! Hands up.
求你们别开枪
Please, don't shoot.
我有需要我的家人
I-I-I have a family who needs me.
求求了
Please.
你住在那里吗
You staying over there?
-不  -你怎么躲过巡逻队的
- No. - How'd you avoid the patrols?
什么
What?
一直有士兵在寻找你这样的人
There's been soldiers looking for people like you.
你怎么躲过他们的
How'd you avoid them?
我不知道那是什么意思
I-I don't know what that means.
那你对我们来说没用了
Then you're of no use to us.
你不知道我们经历过什么
You don't know what we've been through.
我妻子受了很重的伤
My wife is hurt real bad.
我不能一边照顾她一边找食物
I can't -- I can't care for her and look for food.
求你们放我走
Please just -- just let me go.
带我们去看看
Show us
不然我就射死你  再去找你的家人
or I'll shoot and find your family later.
好
Okay.
求你们别伤害我们
Just please don't hurt us.
走
Move.
肖呼叫教皇
Shaw to Pope.
-等等  -请讲  肖
- Hold up. - Go ahead, Shaw.
我们在树林里发现了一个男人
We found a man in the woods.
不确定他是否属于目标团伙
Not sure if he's a part of our targets.
他要带我们去见他的人
He's taking us to his people.
你想要我们怎么处理
How do you want us to engage?
杀掉他们
Kill them.
收到
Copy that.
走
Move.
我理解你现在的感受
You know, I feel for you in all of this.
你也许认为我在胡说
You might think that's bullshit,
但这是真的
but it's true.
怎讲
How's that?
我不是机器人  李
I'm not a robot, Rhee.
看到你的朋友们变成行尸很不好受
It sucks to see your friends as walkers.
这就够受的了
And that would be enough.
而你打算做一些疯狂的事
But you are about to do some crazy shit
闯进一个你建立并失去的社区
and break into a community that you built and lost.
我理解的
I get it.
我们失去各自社区的方式非常不同
Your community and mine were lost in very different ways.
你以为我不知道被屠杀的一方是什么感受吗
You think I don't understand the losing side of a massacre?
在与总督的战争中(S06E12)中  瑞克曾率人屠杀卫星站
卫星站里没有儿童
There were no children at the satellite station.
没有家庭
No families.
格雷西父亲为救世军  被瑞克所杀(S08E02)
那亚伦是从哪里找到格雷西的
Then where'd Aaron get Gracie?
你以为我不知道吗
You think I don't know about that?
你不能跟我讨论作战计划
You can't debate battle plans with me.
残忍的程度
Levels of cruelty.
我只想说  我记得
Look, all I'm saying is that I remember
我的家园被侵略  我的人被杀时的情景
when my home was invaded and my people were killed.
那些人  他们也有朋友
Those men -- they had friends.
他们也有女朋友
They had girlfriends.
他们亲友的悲痛是我无法抚平的
People that felt a loss that I couldn't heal.
我不得不向他们交代
And I had to explain to them why --
为什么他们的领袖没能保护好他们
why their leader failed to protect them.
你杀过有家人的人
You killed people who had families.
而且你是在他们家人面前杀的
And you did it in front of their families.
对
Yeah.
是的
I did.
但世界现在不同了  玛姬
But the world is different now, Maggie.
自己人和敌人都更少了
Fewer people to fight for, fight with.
见鬼  能争夺的东西也更少了
Hell, there's fewer things to fight over.
你是说要是换现在  你的做法会不同吗
Are you saying you'd do things differently?
对
Yeah.
对  如果重来一次
Yeah, if I could do it all over again...
我会杀光你们所有人
...I'd have killed every single one of you.
你为什么要这样说
Why would you say that?
这是真相
It's the truth.
为了保护自己人  我们必须不择手段
We got to do whatever we can to protect our people, right?
所以我们才会来这里
I mean, that's why we're here.
所以我们才在做这事
That's why we're doing this.
你为什么要对我说这种话
Why would you say that to me?
你和我今天相处得很好
We had a good day, you and I.
要想办成这事  玛姬  唯一的方法是
And the only way this works, Maggie, is --
我们要坦诚相待
is if we're honest.
他们要把尸体搬去哪
Where do they bring these, exactly?
我不知道
Uh, I don't know.
远离农田和水源的地方吧
Somewhere far from the fields and the water supply.
朋友们
Friends!
非常感激
Much gratitude.
你们帮我干完了我的活儿
I see you've done all my work for me.
而我竟然没带点棒棒糖来
And I didn't even bring you lollipops.
等等
Wait.
你不吃吗
You don't want one?
我吃过好几根了
Oh, I have had several.
-情况如何  -又活过来了
- So, how was it? - Good as new.
给我开了抗生素  止痛药  输液
I got antibiotics, painkillers, IV fluids.
真心感谢你  朋友
Thank you, truly, friend.
乐意效劳
Happy to do it.
很高兴你们都没事
Glad everyone's okay.
你们可以接受新任务了吗
You feel up to a new assignment or --
可以
Yes!
放马过来
Bring it on.
史蒂芬妮  尤金
Stephanie, Eugene,
我想要你们去清理北围栏
I'd like you to clear the area up along the north fence line.
-你能带他去吗  -当然
- Can you show him? - Yeah, sure.
非常好
Excellent.
以西结  公主  跟我来
Ezekiel, Princess, come with me.
玛姬
Maggie.
好消息
Good news.
还在那里
It's still there.
你遇到他们的人了吗
You run into any of them?
没有
No.
那边看起来没问题
That looks good over there.
来吧
Come on, man.
这个交给我
I got this one.
尤金
Eugene!
谢谢  搭档
Thanks, partner.
-团队合作最重要  -对
- Teamwork is all. - Yeah.
这是在搞什么
What the hell was that about?
你们打扰了我们的约会
You just disrupted our date.
不好意思
Excuse me.
我们刚救了你们的命
We just saved your life.
私人警卫能保护我们
We have private security for that.
尤金  走吧  他们...
Eugene, let's go. They're --
你猜怎么着  这主意很好
You know what? Best idea yet.
你没理由这么无礼  伙计
Well, there's no reason to be so rude, hoss.
伙计
Hoss?
天啊  抱歉
Oh, my God. Sorry.
我只是不习惯和庶民讲话  所以
I'm just not used to talking to a plebeian, so this is --
有人在拽词啊
Oh, someone used their dictionary today.
-尤金  -稍等
- Hey, Eugene. - Now, just a minute.
我们应该得到感谢或道歉
We have earned either gratitude or an apology,
就看这位年轻人先说哪句了
whichever this young man can muster first.
-尤金  -你以为你是谁
- Eugene. - Who the hell do you think that you are?
我正在和一个
I think I'm talking to someone who's being
-非常无礼的人说话  -尤金
- extremely rude right now. - Eugene.
稍等片刻
Now just hold your horses one second.
-你根本不知道你在和谁说话  -尤金
- You have no idea who you're talking to right now. - Eugene.
我知道  我在和一个小男人说话
Oh, I think I do, and that would be a tiny, little man.
你很聪明是吧
You're so smart.
蠢婊子
You stupid bitch!
看你对我的女友做了什么
Look what you just did to my girlfriend!
老天  你做了什么
Oh, my God! What did you do?!
这家伙太混球了
This guy was being, well, an asshole.
-我们很抱歉  -别碰我
- Look, we're -- we're so sorry. - No, don't touch!
我们一直在不间断地工作
We've been working without a break,
他不是有意的
and he didn't mean to.
这里发生了什么
What the hell happened here?
看看他们对凯拉做了什么
Look what they did to Kayla.
这俩疯子袭击了我们
These lunatics attacked us.
都是你的错  墨瑟
You know, this is all your fault, Mercer.
你他妈的跑哪去了
Where the hell were you?!
我背后都是该死的腐尸
I had goddamn rotters up my ass!
然后这个蠢货过来攻击了我
And then this dumb shit rolled up and attacked me.
这错得非常离谱
That is categorically untrue.
你打他了吗
Did you hit him?
-是的  但是  -你在想什么
- Yes, but - What the hell were you thinking?
你不知道他是谁吗
Don't you know who that is?
我是奥村由美子
Hi. I'm Yumiko Okumura.
我是来见弥尔顿女士的
I'm here for my meeting with Ms. Milton.
感谢你准时到来
Thank you for being on time.
弥尔顿女士对她的日程安排非常严格
Ms. Milton is fastidious about her schedule.
你想喝草药茶吗
Would you like an herbal tea?
不  谢了
No, thank you.
气泡水或浓咖啡呢
Sparkling water or espresso?
不用了
No. I'm alright.
请坐
Please, have a seat.
《美好假日-意大利别墅赏鉴》
西西里帕切科  圣托马索别墅
拉齐奥蒂沃利  埃斯泰别墅
你是新来的那组人的一员  对吗
You're part of the new group that came in, right?
对  我猜是吧
Yeah. I guess.
你们安顿得还好吗
Are you all settling in okay?
嗯  我几天没见过朋友们了  所以
Yeah. I mean, I haven't seen my friends in a few days, so...
对此我很遗憾  他们还好吗
I'm sorry to hear that. Is everyone okay?
喂
Yes?
是的  当然  我立刻办
Yes. Of course. I'll --  I'll do it now.
一切还好吗
Is everything okay?
弥尔顿女士恐怕要重新安排会面了
I'm afraid Ms. Milton will have to reschedule.
有人刚袭击了她儿子
Someone just attacked her son.
在那种情况下
Situation like that,
你应该救他
you're supposed to save him,
保护总管的儿子
protect the governor's son.
你本可以成为英雄的
You'd have been a hero.
你本可以提出任何要求的
You could have asked for anything.
我道歉
My apologies.
我没推导出这样的结论
I did not ascertain such a conclusion.
好  不逗你了
Alright, no more screwing around.
你想出去
You want out,
现在代价更高了
now the price is higher.
我需要你们城镇的名字和位置
I need the name of your town and how to get there.
这超过了我的权限
T-That is beyond my purview.
那么欢迎了
Then welcome.
这里就是家
This is home.
你的朋友们可以继续杀行尸
Your friends can keep killing walkers.
你老家的人  不管他们在哪里
Your people, wherever they are,
只能自力更生了
can figure things out on their own.
如果我说出坐标
I-If I were to disclose those coordinates,
你能为我的社区提供什么样的安全保障
what guarantee could you provide for my community's safety?
看看周围
Look around.
想想我们是如何对待你的
Think how we've treated you.
你获得了多少次机会
All the chances you've gotten.
这没有直接回答我的疑问
That's not a directly reply to my query.
随你吧
Up to you.
等等
Wait.
看吧
See?
我说的都是实话
I told you the truth.
求你们别伤害我们
Please don't hurt us.
你得带上你的儿子逃走
You need to take your son and run.
永远别再回来
Don't ever come back here.
跟你爸走
Go with your dad.
走吧  亲爱的
Go ahead, honey.
别怕
Don't be afraid.
没事的
It's okay.
我爱你
I love you.
走吧
Go.
感谢上帝你们来了
Oh, thank God for you.
祂回应了我的祈祷
He answered my prayers.
我活着他们是永远不会走的
They were never gonna leave while I was still alive,
他们留在这里很危险
and it was dangerous for them to stay.
我准备好了
I'm ready.
拜托了
Please.
你怎么对教皇说
What are you gonna tell Pope?
你杀了他们
That you killed them.
这对你是好事
It'll be good for you.
莉娅  我要告诉你一件事
Look, Leah, there's something I need to tell you.
回复  肖
Come in, Shaw.
肖  完毕
Shaw. Over.
我们需要你立刻回来
We need you back ASAP.
我们得走了
We gotta go.